{
  "questionBank": [
    {
      "question": "What is The Capital of Florida ?",
      "a": "Albany",
      "b": "Tallahassee",
      "c": "Atlanta",
      "d": "Dover",
      "correctAnswer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country gifted the Statue of Liberty to the US??",
      "a": "Austria",
      "b": "Germany",
      "c": "France",
      "d": "Italy",
      "correctAnswer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is the cost of gas in florida?",
      "a": "$4",
      "b": "$3",
      "c": "$5",
      "d": "too damn high",
      "correctAnswer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "April zodiac sign is Taurus what month is she born on ?",
      "a": "January",
      "b": "March",
      "c": "February",
      "d": "April",
      "correctAnswer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "which is the best dog breed?",
      "a": "yorkie",
      "b": "German Shepherd",
      "c": "Poodle",
      "d": "Rottweiler",
      "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Finish the phrase: you will know  ",
      "a": "gorge",
      "b": "alex",
      "c": "jesus",
      "d": "david",
      "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "which following Iphone does not exist?",
      "a": "iphone 14 ",
      "b": "iphone 5",
      "c": "iphone 8 ",
      "d": "iphone 9 ",
      "correctAnswer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "which the flowing music genre get the most hate",
      "a": "Rap music",
      "b": "christian music",
      "c": "rock music",
      "d": "Country music",
      "correctAnswer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "Finish the phrase:when in doubt choose ",
      "a": "A",
      "b": "B",
      "c": "C",
      "d": "D",
      "correctAnswer": "c"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "is ever ok to text:asdfghjkl ?",
      "a": "no",
      "b": "your geting block",
      "c": "sometime",
      "d": "never",
      "correctAnswer": "b"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "was this radom quiz fun?",
      "a": "no",
      "b": "yes",
      "c": "naw",
      "d": " nooo",
      "correctAnswer": "b"
    }
  ]
}
